https://puppyfinder.com/privacy_policy

Privacy Policy
We at PUPPYFINDER.com have created this privacy policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to
protecting your personal information and informing you about how we handle it. This privacy policy
only applies to transactions and activities in which you engage, and data gathered, on the
PUPPYFINDER.com Website. Please review this privacy policy periodically as we may modify it from
time to time. Each time you visit the Site or provide us with information, by doing so you are
accepting the practices described in this privacy policy at that time.
Your IP Address:
Like most e-commerce Websites, each time you visit the
Site, we automatically collect your IP address and the web page from which you came. In order to
administer and optimize the Site for you and to diagnose problems with our Site, we use your IP
address to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information about you.
Cookies:
Like most Websites, the Site uses cookies to keep track of your
purchases and other activity on the Site and enhance your experience on the Site. We also use
cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password, and if you choose,
to save other personal information so you do not have to reenter it each time you visit the
Site. Third party advertisers on the Site may also place or read cookies on your browser. If you
wish to disable these cookies, the "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you
how. However, if you set your browser to disable cookies, you may not be able to access certain
areas on the Site.
Information We Collect From You:
In order to operate the Site and to
provide you with information about products or services that may be of interest to you, we may
collect "personal information" (i.e. information that could be used to contact you directly
(without using the Site) such as full name, postal address, phone number or email address),
"financial information" (i.e. credit card numbers or passwords) or "demographic information"
(i.e. information that you submit, or that we collect, that is neither personal information nor
financial information; this may include, but is not limited to, zip code, postal code, hometown,
gender, username, age/birth date, purchase history information, browsing history information,
searching history information, registration history information, and the content of
communications between you and other members over the Site), subject to the rest of this
paragraph. Demographic information is divided into two categories:
"non-public information",
"public information",
which consists of all other demographic information.
Information Other Websites Collect From You:
On the Site, we place links to
other Websites operated by other parties. Some of these other Websites contain our brand names
and trademarks and other intellectual property that we own; others do not. When you click on
these links and visit these other Websites, regardless of whether or not they contain our brand
names, trademarks and other intellectual property, you need to be aware that we do not control
these other Websites or these other Websites' business practices, and that this privacy policy
does not apply to these other Websites. Consequently, the operators of these other Websites may
collect different kinds of information about you, and may use and disclose that information in
different ways than we would if it were collected on the Site. We encourage you to review their
privacy policies and remind you that we will not be responsible for their actions.
How We Use Personal Information:
We use your email address and your other
personal information to help us efficiently operate the Site, to contact you in connection
with your transactions and other activities on the Site (including, but not limited to,
confirmation emails or important news that could affect your relationship with
PUPPYFINDER.com), and to forward messages to you from other PUPPYFINDER.com users. These
types of communications are known as "Operational Communications." In some cases,
Operational Communications may also contain commercial messages, such as banner ads and
special offers.
To operate the Site, including processing your transactions and supporting your activities on
the Site, we may share your personal information with our agents, representatives,
contractors and service providers so they can provide us with support services such as
authorization of credit card transactions, email origination, receipt or support services,
customer relationship management services, order fulfillment and sweepstakes and promotional
fulfillment. We require these entities not to use your information for any other
purpose.
By purchasing, or registering or making reservations for, products or services offered or
sponsored by third parties on the Site, or electing to receive communications (such as
emails notifications) or electing to participate in contests, sweepstakes or other programs
(such as discount or rewards programs), offered or sponsored by third parties on the Site,
you consent to our providing your personal information to those third parties. Those third
parties may use your personal information in accordance with their own privacy policies. You
will need to contact those third parties to instruct them directly regarding your
preferences for the use of your personal information by them. Additionally, you agree that
we may use and disclose all such information so submitted to such third parties in the same
manner in which we are entitled to use and disclose any other information you submit to
us.
In some cases, we may enter into a promotional relationship with another company in which we
prominently display their brand name or trademarks on pages of the Site. These pages are
known as "Co-Branded Pages" and these companies are known as "Co-Branded Companies." If the
page on which you submit information is a Co-Branded Page, or was accessed by clicking on a
link on a Co-Branded Page, then we may share your personal information with the associated
Co-Branded Company. Co-Branded Companies may use your personal information in accordance
with their own privacy policies. You will need to contact Co-Branded Companies to instruct
them directly regarding your preferences for the use of your personal information by them.
Additionally, you agree that we may use and disclose all such information so submitted to
such Co-Branded Companies in the same manner in which we are entitled to use and disclose
any other information you submit to us. Some Co-Branded Pages may contain an action tag
(also known as a Web Beacon or a 1 pixel .gif file) that a third party, such as the
advertising Company X, may use to read cookies that it, or its clients, may have placed on
your browser at other (non-PUPPYFINDER.com) web sites before your visit to PUPPYFINDER.com.
This technology is used to measure the effectiveness of advertisements on such other
Websites that promote Co-Branded Pages. Further, Company X, or such other third parties, may
use the information collected through this technology to learn more about your visits to
this Site and other Websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of
interest to you. We have been informed by Company X that unless you are otherwise notified,
they do not use your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number, and do not link your
online actions to any information that can be used to identify or contact you. However, as
we may not verify that this is the case, we ask that you seek Company X's assurances
yourself and do not hold us accountable for the accuracy of the above statement.
Any third party with whom we are allowed to share your personal information is authorized to
use your personal information in accordance with our contractual arrangements with such
third parties and in accordance with their own privacy policies, over which we have no
control, and you agree that we are not responsible or liable for any of their actions or
omissions. Those who contact you will need to be instructed directly by you regarding your
preferences for the use of your personal information by them.
Please read the information below under the heading "Special Cases in which we Share Personal
and Financial Information" to learn more ways in which we may share your personal
information.
How We Use Financial Information:
We use your financial information to
check your qualifications, to bill you for products and services and to enable you to
participate in discount, rebate and similar programs in which you may elect to participate. By
making a purchase, or engaging in any other kind of activity or transaction that uses financial
information, on the Site, you consent to our providing your financial information to our service
providers and to such third parties as we determine are necessary to support and process your
activities and transactions, as well as to your credit card issuer for their purposes. These
third parties may include the credit card companies and banking institutions used to process and
support the transaction or activity. By purchasing, or registering or making reservations for,
products or services of third parties offered on the Site, or by participating in programs
offered on the Site that are administered by third parties and that require you to submit
financial information in order to use them, you also consent to our providing your financial
information to those third parties. Additionally, if the page on which you submit information is
a Co-Branded Page, or was accessed by clicking on a link on a Co-Branded Page, then we may share
your financial information with the associated Co-Branded Company. Any of these various third
parties (including Co-Branded Companies) may be authorized to use your financial information in
accordance with our contractual arrangements with such third parties and in accordance with
their own privacy policies, over which we have no control, and you agree that we are not
responsible or liable for any of their actions or omissions. Additionally, you agree that we may
use and disclose all such information so submitted to such third parties in the same manner in
which we are entitled to use and disclose any other information that you submit to us. Please
read the information below under the heading "Special Cases in which we Share Personal and
Financial Information" to learn more ways in which we may share your financial information.
Special Cases in which we Share Personal and Financial Information:
Your
personal information or financial information may be passed on to a third party in the event of
a transfer of ownership or assets, or a bankruptcy. We may also disclose personal information or
financial information when we determine that such disclosure is necessary to comply with
applicable law, to cooperate with law enforcement or to protect the interests or safety of
PUPPYFINDER.com or other visitors to the Site. We also may disclose your personal information or
financial information to our subsidiary and parent companies and businesses, and other
affiliated legal entities and businesses with whom we are under common control. Whenever
personal information or financial information is disclosed under this paragraph, we may also
disclose your demographic information along with it, on a non-anonymous basis. All of our
parent, subsidiary and affiliated legal entities and businesses that receive your personal
information, financial information, or non-anonymous demographic information from us will comply
with the terms of this privacy policy with respect to their use and disclosure of such
information.
How We Use Public Information and Other Demographic Information:
We may
review all demographic information. We may use public information to enable other users to find
your profile and to communicate with you. We may use demographic information to tailor the Site
and communications to your interests. We may also share demographic information with advertisers
on an anonymous and aggregated basis (i.e., without telling the advertisers your identity). One
of the reasons we may do this is to increase the likelihood that our advertisers' goods and
services will appeal to PUPPYFINDER.com's users, so that we may target specific ads at specific
demographic groups. Our sharing of demographic information with advertisers is anonymous (i.e.,
we do not tell advertisers which particular PUPPYFINDER.com users are members of which
demographic groups), subject to the rest of this privacy policy. When you respond to an
advertisement, however, we ask you to remember that if that ad that is targeted to a demographic
group and you decide to give the advertiser your personal information, then the advertiser may
be able to identify you as being a member of that demographic group. Please also be aware that
when we disclose your financial information or personal information to a Co-Branded Company, as
described above, we may also disclose to that Co-Branded Company your demographic information,
other than the content of one-on-one communications between you and other members. Please also
be aware that we may disclose your demographic information on a non-anonymous basis as described
above in the paragraph titled "Special Cases in which we Share Personal and Financial
Information." Also, to read further details about how we may use your public information, see
our Terms of Use.
Changing our Privacy Policy for Previously Gathered Information:
If at any
point we decide to use particular personally identifiable information in a manner different from
that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email or by
providing 30 day notice on the Site. Please note that we will continue to have the right to
change our privacy policy and practices, and how we use your personally identifiable
information, without notice, as described in the first paragraph of this Privacy Policy,
provided that such changes shall only apply to information gathered on or after the date of the
change.
If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy, the practices of the Site, or your
dealings with the Site, you can contact us at
legal@PUPPYFINDER.com.
Breeders
USACanadaUnited KingdomAustraliaWorldwideEuropeAlbaniaAndorraAustriaAzerbaijanBelarusBelgiumBosnia and HerzegovinaBulgariaCroatiaCyprusDenmarkEstoniaFaroe IslandsFinlandFranceGeorgiaGermanyGreeceHungaryIcelandIrelandItalyLatviaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacedoniaMaltaMoldovaMonacoMontenegroNetherlandsNorwayPolandPortugalRomainiaRussiaSan MarinoSerbiaSlovakiaSloveniaSpainSvalbardSwedenSwitzerlandUkraineAmericasAnguillaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaBahamasBarbadosBelizeBermudaBoliviaBrazilCayman IslandsChileColombiaCosta RicaDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEl SalvadorFrench GuianaGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuatemalaGuyanaHondurasJamaicaMartiniqueMexicoMontserratNicaraguaPanamaParaguayPeruSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Pierre and MiquelonSt Vincent and the GrenadinesSurinameTrinidad and TobagoUruguayVenezuelaAsia PacificArmeniaBahrainBhutanBruneiCambodiaChinaCook IslandsFijiFrench PolynesiaHong KongIndiaIndonesiaIsraelJapanJordanKazakhstanKiribatiKuwaitKyrgyzstanLaosMalaysiaMaldivesMarshall IslandsMicronesiaMongoliaNauruNepalNew CaledoniaNew ZealandOmanPalauPapua New GuineaPhilippinesQatarSamoaSaudi ArabiaSingaporeSolomon IslandsKorea, SouthSri LankaTaiwanTajikistanThailandTongaTurkmenistanTuvaluUnited Arab EmiratesVanuatuVietnamWallis and FutunaYemen
Keywords
Gender
Male
Female
Price Range
From
$
To
Puppyfinder.com no longer supports your browser. Please upgrade your browser.
This member has successfully passedidentity verification by a third party provider
Phone Verified
This member has successfully passedphone verification by a third party provider
PayPal Verified
This member is an owner of a verified PayPal account
Not Verified
This user's identity has not been verified.
Featured Listing
This Featured Listing has the highest priority placementon all search result and high-traffic pages of the site.
Premium Listing
This Premium Listing has a high priority placement,appearing above all basic verified and non-verified ads.
Gold Breeder
This dog breeder is a subscriber to the Gold Plan
Silver Breeder
This dog breeder is a subscriber to the Silver Plan
